techreport.com 2007-06-26

# The Tech Report

Five flavors of Intel's P35 Express compared  
  
Intel's Core 2 Duo E6750 processor  
  
Western Digital's Caviar SE16 750GB hard drive  
  
AMD's Athlon X2 BE-2350 processor  
  
Intel's 'V8' media creation platform  
  
GeForce 8600 series graphics cards compared  
  
Intel's P35 Express chipset  
  
**More...** | 

The Tech Report's Privacy Policy  
The Tech Report, LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for http://techreport.com. 

The bottom line  
Personal information (such as your name, address, and email address) that you entrust to The Tech Report will not be shared with any third party without your explicit permission to do so. We do not sell our mailing lists, nor do we rent them to third parties, under any conditions. 

The Tech Report's forums and news comments systems use common cookie technology to store your preferences on your computer, at your option. We may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. 

Third-party advertisers  
Some advertisements at The Tech Report are served by third-party advertising networks. Some of these companies may use common cookie technology to place a cookie on your computer. This information is used to serve ads to you on this site and possibly others. The Tech Report cannot control or be responsible for this third-party data, but we do seek to do business only with companies that handle such data responsibly. 

Links  
This site contains links to other sites. The Tech Report is not responsible for either the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

Exceptions  
Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose personal information to necessary third parties if we are required to do so: 

  1. To comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order;
  2. To protect the company's rights and property;
  3. To investigate reports of users sending material using a false e-mail address or users sending harassing, threatening, or abusive messages;
  4. To protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our site and/or any of our services; or
  5. During emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.

Policy changes  
The Tech Report may, in the future, modify this privacy policy in order to provide additional clarity or to address additional issues, as needed. Any such changes will be posted here immediately. 

Contacting us  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with The Tech Report, you can contact: 

The Tech Report, LLC  
1322 SE Princeton Drive  
Lee’s Summit, MO 64081  
USA  
damage@techreport.com  

| 

Poll: Do you play games on your PC or console(s)?  
  
Intel's Core 2 Duo E6750 processor  
  
Saturday science subject: Space tourism  
  
Vista Home Basic is a no go for virtualization  
  
Quake Wars will have in-game ads  
  
Analysts think AMD could pull out of manufacturing  
  
First Vista Service Pack may face delays  
  
**More...**
